Santiago Cervan Full Stack Developer

Email: santicervan@live.com WhatsApp: +54.3517380506 Córdoba - Argentina.

Portfolio: santiago-cervan-portfolio.vercel.app LinkedIn GitLab GitHub

I am a Front End web developer with strong skills in designing and developing responsive web pages, focusing on optimization and speed. I also have experience in implementing Back End to Front End functionalities. My approach is user-centered, creating user-friendly and intuitive interfaces that enhance the user experience.

I am self-reliant in researching and selecting suitable libraries and frameworks, quickly adapting to the required technologies by the company. I am organized in task management and utilize the Scrum methodology for effective communication and meeting deadlines.

TECH SKILLS

Javascript, Typescript, React, NextJs, Redux, Node.js, HTML, CSS, Express, Postgres, Sequelize, Stripe.

SOFT SKILLS

Leadership, adaptability, empathy, public speaking, open-mindedness, planning and organization, creativity, decision-making, teamwork, effective communication.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Voike Music – Front-end Developer (Part-time)

october 2023 - present

- Layout and design optimization.
- Performance and SEO improvements.
- Efficient Git Flow management for effective version control.
- Integration with Backend Endpoints.
- Front-end functionality development.
- Support for the company's legacy projects.

<u>Global Think Technology</u> – Front-end Developer (Temporary)

october 2023 - december 2023

- Integration with Backend Endpoints.
- Front-end functionality development.
- Efficient Git Flow management for effective version control.
- Support for the company's legacy projects.

Noa Experience – Front-end Developer (Full-time)

october 2022 - october 2023

- Layout and design optimization, enhancing user experience, and reducing load times.
- Efficient Git Flow management for effective version control.
- Initiating new projects.
- Integration with Backend Endpoints.
- Front-end functionality development.
- Support for the company's legacy projects.

PROJECTS

<u>Voike</u>

october 2023 – december 2023

Voike Music, Bogotá, Colombia.

- · Refactoring old code.
- Applying SEO strategies to improve positioning.
- Enhancing performance by refactoring code and optimizing multimedia resources.
- Web development using NextJs with JavaScript and Tailwind for the Front-end.

<u>Omuni</u>

october 2023 - december 2023

Global Think Technology, Córdoba, Argentina.

- Implementing new functionalities for a communication system.
- Front-end development using ReactJs with TypeScript, and Styled Components for designs.

<u>Electa</u>

january 2022 - october 2023

Noa Experience, Bogotá, Colombia.

- Initiated the project, managed the repository, implemented Git Flow, designed, developed, and implemented
 functionalities for a social media web application targeting followers of political candidates in Colombia.
 Features include registration (Google or Facebook), login, news panel, multimedia, surveys, referrals, profile
 editing, challenges, etc.
- Developed the app using Next.js with TypeScript and Tailwind CSS.

Iunctus

december 2022 - february 2023

Noa Experience, Bogotá, Colombia.

- Initiated the project, managed the repository, implemented Git Flow, designed, developed, and implemented functionalities for a system to track law projects and chamber members. Features include date-based searches, filters, sorting, login, administrator role, project creation, editing, and deletion.
- Developed the app using Next.js with TypeScript and Tailwind CSS.

Weeki

october 2022 - december 2022

Noa Experience, Bogotá, Colombia.

- Designed, developed, and implemented functionalities for a web application focused on apartment rentals in Bogotá, Colombia. Features include date-based searches, reservations, online payments, etc.
- Developed the app using Next.js with TypeScript and Tailwind CSS.

PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION

Senior technician in programming – <u>Teclab</u>

august 2023 - present

Tertiary education

Full Stack Web Developer - Henry Bootcamp

may 2022 - september 2022

Intensive bootcamp of over 800 hours of coding

Introduction to Programming - Argentina Programa

march 2022 - may 2022

Introductory programming course

LANGUAGES

Native Spanish speaker.

English (C1 Advanced).

English Certificate 68/100 (C1 Advanced) - EFSET

september 2022

Link to certificate: **EFSET Certificate**